XXX-Redacted/DATE tXXX-Redacted/Gender XXX-Redacted/GPE police report detailing XXX-Redacted/PERSON's alleged armed robbery of two memorabilia dealers. 
TXXX-Redacted/Gender document provides a compreXXX-Redacted/Gendernsive account of tXXX-Redacted/Gender probe of tXXX-Redacted/Gender September 13 incident in a room at tXXX-Redacted/Gender Palace Station hotel, 
and includes details of interviews with XXX-Redacted/PERSON, businessmen XXX-Redacted/PERSON and XXX-Redacted/PERSON, and XXX-Redacted/PERSON, tXXX-Redacted/Gender ex-con who XXX-Redacted/Genderlped orcXXX-Redacted/Genderstrate XXX-Redacted/PERSON's bid to recover what XXX-Redacted/Gender claims were stolen items.
 TXXX-Redacted/Gender report, which notes that XXX-Redacted/PERSON was 'extremely welcoming' to detectives wXXX-Redacted/Gendern tXXX-Redacted/Gendery met with XXX-Redacted/Gender at tXXX-Redacted/Gender Palms hotel, quotes tXXX-Redacted/Gender athlete calling Beardsley 'certifiable.' Referring to tXXX-Redacted/Gender dealers's attempts to sell XXX-Redacted/Gender belongings, XXX-Redacted/PERSON said, 'TXXX-Redacted/Gendery sneakin'.' Denying that XXX-Redacted/Gender was involved in an armed robbery, XXX-Redacted/PERSON said that XXX-Redacted/Gender went to tXXX-Redacted/Gender hotel to recover 'family stuff.' 'My All American ball!,' XXX-Redacted/Gender said. 'I would never give that away!' As XXX-Redacted/PERSON was being transported by detectives following XXX-Redacted/Gender arrest,
 XXX-Redacted/Gender noted that XXX-Redacted/Gender came to XXX-Redacted/GPE and 'look what happened, I got arrested.'